Bujar Ademi

CONTACT

Osogovo 2 Kumanovo North Macedonia bujar@bujarademi.com http://bujarademi.com +389 70 245 743

OBJECTIVE

Experienced Software Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer Software industry. Skilled in .NET, Databases, Azure, Windows Server, and Web Services API. Able to effectively self-manage during independent project, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

LinkPlus IT, Pristina / KS

March 2018 — Present

Senior C# .NET Developer

- Development for Canadian company (Lixar IT) mainly on aviation and sport division
 - Worked to solve complex problems using the latest Azure web technologies
 - Performed automated testing tasks and developed complex features routinely
 - Worked on software changes and alterations based on specific design specifications
 - Effectively addressed complex bugs
- Developed PrintService, desktop application for printing with print drivers or raw printing for various templates for betting software.

Technologies used:

- **■** C#
- Web Api
- SQL Server 2016 and Azure databases
- Unit tests
- Azure services
- Jira
- Bitbucket
- Dependency injection (Autofac, Unity)

Validata Holdings, Athens / GR

February 2018 — July 2018

Senior Software Developer

- Worked productively with Product Team to understand requirements and business specifications around ATS Suit, software for testing T24 Temenos core banking software
- Effectively coded software changes and alterations based on specific design specifications for COB
 Monitoring tool
- Implemented and updated application module under the direction of product owner

Technologies used:

- **■** C#
- SOAP Web Services
- XML
- Visual Basic .NET
- **■** (++
- WebApi

Bujar Ademi

Senior C# .NET Developer

- Organizing work
- Responsible for developing projects, collect requirements from clients
- Developed web application E-Learning Management System
- Developer online invoicing web app

Technologies used:

- C#
- WebAPi
- SQL Server
- Javascript & jQuery
- Visual Basic .NET
- Entity Framework
- SignalR

DelCo DOOEL, Skopje / MK

July 2011 — March 2017

Senior C# .NET Developer

- Developed main system (ERP and CRM) for tracking and evidence of shipments
- Invoicing system
- Time attendance of employees and human resources
- Module for reading pdf files (itextsharp library)
- Developed web application for clients to track and send online notifications for new shipments
- Developed system for law firm, Konrad & Partners, for importing/exporting, mass printing and tracking creditor claims from the beginning process until enforcement process (main creditor EVN Macedonia)
- Configuration and maintenance of Windows Servers
 - Active Directory
 - File Server
 - IIS
 - SQL Server
 - Backup servers
- Configuration and maintenance of networks
 - Sophos firewall
 - VPN Links with 15 offices outside Skopje and Vienna
 - Networking
 - Subnet

Technologies used:

- C#
- Visual Basic .NET
- SQL Server
- .NET Web Forms
- SOAP Web Services
- WebApi
- SignalR

AccountTech, Boston / USA

August 2015 — November 2015

Senior VB.NET Developer

- Third level support
- Analyzing code and finding bugs
- Creating new functions and reports for clients
- Developed system for support team

Bujar Ademi

Creating stored procedures, functions and triggers in sql server

Technologies used:

- Visual Basic .NET
- SQL Server 2014
- MS Access (VBA)
- Stored procedures
- Triggers
- Sql functions

G.S. Limited Group LLC, Tampa / USA

June 2014 — July 2014

Development Lead

- Developed warehouse inventory management system and synchronization with Amazon Marketplace for Online shopping in amazon.com
- Image resize/crop, add watermark to images for Amazon shop
- Various modules for inventory

It was requested by my general manager to go in US and work in this project for his client.

Technologies used:

- C# with .NET 3.5
- SQL Server 2008 R2
- Windows Forms
- Stored procedures
- Triggers
- Sql Functions

EDUCATION

Computer science and technologies

2005 - 2010

South East European University, Tetovo / MK

LANGUAGES

- Albanian
- Macedonian
- English

Bujar Ademi 3